<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml version="2.0">
	
	<category>
	    <pattern>SOFTENG</pattern>
	    <template>
	        <delay>3</delay>The role of software engineer seems to be a great fit for you!
	        You are imaginative, analytical, and an extrovert which makes you a perfect candidate!
	        Software engineers take the role of building, upkeeping, and maintaining a code repository.
	        Your expected salary is $109,020 according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
	        Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>DATAANALYST</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>A data analyst role would be perfect for you!
            You are imaginative, analytical, and an introvert which makes you a perfect candidate!
            Data analysts collect and clean unorganzied data to present it in a meaningful manner.
            Your expected salary is $100,910 according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>WEBDESIGN</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>Role the drums... <delay>2</delay> web designer!
            You are imaginative, not analytical, and an extrovert!
            Web designers focuses on the front end of the web development process by modernizing and upkeeping web content. 
            Web designers make an estimated $78,300 annually according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>ITSUPPORT</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>You would make a great fit for IT support!
            IT support help detect problems in computers, monitors, or servers and fixes these issues.
            This type of role can be found in any sector of the economy. 
            IT support specialists make an estimated $56,910 annually according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>CYBER</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>You match with the role of cybersecurity specialist!
            Cyber attacks cost corporations tons of money.
            Cybersecurity specialists help mitigate and prevent cyber attacks by protecting networks and data systems.
            They are a crucial role to a tech company.
            Cybersecurity specialists make an estimated 102,600 annually according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>NETWORKDESIGN</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>You should do more research on becoming a Newtork Designer! 
            Network designers plan, setup, and install servers and other network components for a business.
            Network designers make an estimated $120,520 annually according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>PROJMANAG</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>Consider becoming a Project Manager!
            Project managers meet deadline for goals set by the company through strategic approach.
            There is a lot of communication that goes in this role.
            Project managers make an estimated 94,500 annually according to the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics.
            Hope this helped! To run another questionaire say "continue."
        </template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
        <pattern>ANSWEREDNOTOEVERYTHING</pattern>
        <template>
            <delay>3</delay>Mmmm... you seem to not meet the qualifications for me to recommend you a job in my repository!
            Don't worry! The computer industry is filled with hundreds of unique roles!
            You should considered reevaluating your strengths.
            Whenever you are ready, comeback and say "Hi" for a reevaluation!
        </template>
    </category>
	
</aiml>